A Guide to the Records of the Charlottesville School Board 1869-2006
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series X Deeds, Reports and Records
  - C. Records
    - Teacher Record Books, 1907-1970
      - Teacher Record Books T. Gochenour-M.A. Quarles 1939-1940 Sep-Jan, 4 Items (Box-folder 138:6)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-S.L. Browne 1940 Feb-May, 5 Items (Box-folder 138:7)
      - Teacher Record Books M.Burnet-T. Gochenour 1940 Feb-May, 5 Items (Box-folder 139:1)
      - Teacher Record Books J.E. Jones-G. Shufflebarger 1940 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 139:2)
      - Teacher Record Books I.D. Sinclair-L.P. Woodson 1940 Feb-May, 3 Items (Box-folder 139:3)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-I.W. Boston 1940-1941 Sep-Jan, 4 Items (Box-folder 139:4)
      - Teacher Record Books S.L. Browne-T. Gochenour 1940-1941 Sep-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 139:5)
      - Teacher Record Books J.E. Jones-G. Shufflebarger 1940-1941 Sep-Jan, 4 Items (Box-folder 139:6)
      - Teacher Record Books I.D. Sinclair-L.P. Woodson 1940-1941 Sep-Jan, 4 Items (Box-folder 139:7)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-I.W. Boston 1941 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 140:1)
      - Teacher Record Books S.L. Browne-M.E. Coleman 1941 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 140:2)
      - Teacher Record Books T. Gochenour-M.A. Quarles 1941 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 140:3)
      - Teacher Record Books G. Shufflebarger-L.P. Woodson 1941 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 140:4)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-I.W. Boston 1941-1942 Sep-Jan, 4 Items (Box-folder 140:5)
      - Teacher Record Books S.L. Browne-H.S. Burnley 1941-1942 Sep-Jan, 4 Items (Box-folder 140:6)
      - Teacher Record Books M.E. Coleman-S. Moore 1941-1942 Sep-Jan, 4 Items (Box-folder 141:1)
      - Teacher Record Books M.A. Quarles-M.K. Thacker 1941-1942 Sep-Jan, 4 Items (Box-folder 141:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M.K. Thacker-J.K. Werner 1941-1942 Sep-Jan, 3 Items (Box-folder 141:3)
        Includes Teacher's Monthly Reports
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-I.W. Boston 1942 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 141:4)
      - Teacher Record Books S.L. Browne-H.S. Burnley 1942 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 141:5)
      - Teacher Record Books M.E. Coleman-S. Moore 1942 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 141:6)
      - Teacher Record Books S.L. Browne-H.S. Burnley 1942 Feb-May, 4 Items (Box-folder 141:7)
      - Teacher Record Books M.A. Quarles-J.K. Werner 1942 Feb-May, 5 Items (Box-folder 141:8)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-A.L. Barksdale 1942-1943 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 142:1)
      - Teacher Record Books I.W. Boston-C.C. Burnley 1942-1943 Sep-Jun, 5 Items (Box-folder 142:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M.E. Coleman-Hawkins 1942-1943 Sep-Jun, 3 Items (Box-folder 142:3)
      - Teacher Record Books J. Jones-M.A. Quarles 1942-1943 Sep-Jun, 3 Items (Box-folder 142:4)
      - Teacher Record Books G. Shufflebarger-J. Werner 1942-1943 Sep-Jun, 3 Items (Box-folder 142:5)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Adams-I.W. Boston 1943-1944 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 142:6)
      - Teacher Record Books N. Boswell-M.E. Coleman 1943-1944 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 142:7)
      - Teacher Record Books H. Harvey-J. Jones 1943-1944 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 143:1)
      - Teacher Record Books S. Moore-J.K. Werner 1943-1944 Sep-Jun, 5 Items (Box-folder 143:2)
      - Teacher Record Books L. Bailey-M. Burnet 1944-1945 Sep-Jun, 5 Items (Box-folder 143:3)
      - Teacher Record Books H.S. Burnley-M.B Lythe 1944-1945 Sep-Jun, 6 Items (Box-folder 143:4)
      - Teacher Record Books S. Moore-J.K. Werner 1944-1945 Sep-Jun, 6 Items (Box-folder 143:5)
      - Teacher Record Books L. Bailey-M. Burnet 1945-1946 Sep-Jun, 5 Items (Box-folder 143:6)
      - Teacher Record Books H.S. Burnley-I.D. Johnson 1945-1946 Sep-Jun, 6 Items (Box-folder 144:1)
      - Teacher Record Books S. Moore-J.K. Werner 1945-1946 Sep-Jun, 6 Items (Box-folder 144:2)
      - Teacher Record Books I.W. Boston-M. Trevillian 1946 Jun-July, 4 Items (Box-folder 144:3)
      - Teacher Record Books L. Bailey- M.R. Brierley 1946-1947 Sep-Jun, 5 Items (Box-folder 144:4)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Burnet-A.M. Huffman 1946-1947 Sep-Jun, 5 Items (Box-folder 144:5)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Laughner-M. Rohr 1946-1947 Sep-Jun, 5 Items (Box-folder 144:6)
      - Teacher Record Books L. Bailey-M.R. Brierley 1947-1948 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 145:1)
      - Teacher Record Books G. Shufflebarger-V.P. Woods 1946-1947 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 145:2)
      - Teacher Record Books G. Brock-S.M. Chapman 1947-1948 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 145:3)
      - Teacher Record Books O.L. Cole-E. Laughner 1947-1948 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 145:4)
      - Teacher Record Books S. Moore-M.E. Wood 1947-1948 Sep-Jun, 5 Items (Box-folder 145:5)
      - Teacher Record Books L.K. Bailey-G. Brock 1948-1949 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 145:6)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Burnet-H.G. Deshane 1948-1949 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 145:7)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Guerrant-S. Moore 1948-1949 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 146:1)
      - Teacher Record Books M.E. Rohr-M.E. Wood 1948-1949 Sep-Jun, 5 Items (Box-folder 146:2)
      - Teacher Record Books H. Burnley-S. Irving 1955-1956 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 146:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M.S. McManaway-H. Sadler 1955-1956 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 146:4)
      - Teacher Record Books G. Shufflebarger-E. Woods 1955-1956 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 146:5)
      - Teacher Record Books A.L. Barksdale-L. Coffey 1956-1957 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 146:6)
      - Teacher Record Books N.W. Cole-A.M. Huffman 1956-1957 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 146:7)
      - Teacher Record Books B. Hutton-G. Shufflebarger 1956-1957 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 147:1)
      - Teacher Record Books Smart-E. Wood 1956-1957 Sep-Jun, 4 Items (Box-folder 147:2)
      - Teacher Record Books Oliver 1965-1966, 1 Item (Box-folder 147:3)
      - Teacher Record Books J. Baliles-F.C. Bryant 1965-1966, 3 Items (Box-folder 147:4)
      - Teacher Record Books A.M. Campbell-C. Conner 1965-1966, 4 Items (Box-folder 147:5)
      - Teacher Record Books Evans-V.D. Galgano 1965-1966, 3 Items (Box-folder 147:6)
      - Teacher Record Books N. Gibbons-W.J. Heepe 1965-1966 Walker School, 4 Items (Box-folder 148:1)
      - Teacher Record Books L.B. Leitch-S. Robbins 1965-1966, 3 Items (Box-folder 148:2)
      - Teacher Record Books S. Robbins-E.K. Schollaert 1965-1966, 3 Items (Box-folder 148:3)
      - Teacher Record Books N. Smith-Stacy 1965-1966, 2 Items (Box-folder 148:4)
      - Teacher Record Books H.E. Wainwright-D.G. Wheeler 1965-1966, 3 Items (Box-folder 148:5)
      - Teacher Record Books J. Baliles-Burnet 1966-1967 Walker School, 3 Items (Box-folder 149:1)
      - Teacher Record Books Conley-Dickerman 1966-1967, 3 Items (Box-folder 149:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M.H. Duren-Gardner 1966-1967 Walker School, 3 Items (Box-folder 149:3)
      - Teacher Record Books K.S. Gardner-W.J. Heepe 1966-1967, 3 Items (Box-folder 149:4)
      - Teacher Record Books Hill-L.B. Leitch 1966-1967, 3 Items (Box-folder 149:5)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Macmillan-Motley 1966-1967, 3 Items (Box-folder 150:1)
      - Teacher Record Books D.L. Orr-J. Prince 1966-1967, 3 Items (Box-folder 150:2)
      - Teacher Record Books N.G. Pritchett-Robbins 1966-1967, 3 Items (Box-folder 150:3)
      - Teacher Record Books Robbins-J.A. Saeli 1966-1967, 3 Items (Box-folder 150:4)
      - Teacher Record Books D.P. Samsell-C.B. Snowden 1966-1967, 3 Items (Box-folder 150:5)
      - Teacher Record Books Stancil-J.S. Wagner 1966-1967, 3 Items (Box-folder 151:1)
      - Teacher Record Books B.S. Wescott-A.P. Wood 1966-1967, 3 Items (Box-folder 151:2)
      - Teacher Record Books Kuroghan 1967, 2 Items (Box-folder 151:3)
      - Teacher Record Books E.C. Burnet-E.F. Dickerman 1967-1968, 4 Items (Box-folder 151:4)
      - Teacher Record Books K.S. Gardner-B.S. Hathaway 1967-1968, 3 Items (Box-folder 151:5)
      - Teacher Record Books D.J. Baker-N.E. Evans 1966-1967 Sep-Jun, 6 Items (Box-folder 152:1)
      - Teacher Record Books C. Fentriss-A.M. Johnson 1966-1967 Sep-Jun, 6 Items (Box-folder 152:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Kearney-J.S. Self 1966-1967 Sep-Jun, 6 Items (Box-folder 152:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Smith-W.R. Wilson 1966-1967 Sep-Jun, 7 Items (Box-folder 152:4)
      - Teacher Record Books Office Records N. D., 2 Items (Box-folder 152:5)
      - Teacher Record Books Heepe-L.B. Leitch 1967-1968, 3 Items (Box-folder 153:1)
      - Teacher Record Books A.B. Lugo-D.L. Orr 1967-1968, 3 Items (Box-folder 153:2)
      - Teacher Record Books J. Prince-W.A. Rhodes 1967-1968, 3 Items (Box-folder 153:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M.N. Runkle-Stancil 1967-1968, 3 Items (Box-folder 153:4)
      - Teacher Record Books P.S. Stacy-Whited 1967-1968, 3 Items (Box-folder 153:5)
      - Teacher Record Books D. Bailey-S.E. Barnes 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 154:1)
      - Teacher Record Books J. Bonner-L.M. Brown 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 154:2)
      - Teacher Record Books L.M. Brown-Bufnar 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 154:3)
      - Teacher Record Books Burnet-E.R. Conley 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 154:4)
      - Teacher Record Books Conley-E.F. Dickerman 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 154:5)
      - Teacher Record Books R. Duckett-M.H. Duren 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 155:1)
      - Teacher Record Books K.Gardner-Hatfield 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 155:2)
      - i Teacher Record Books B.S. Hathaway-Horn 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 155:3)
      - Teacher Record Books Irby-C. Jones 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 155:4)
      - Teacher Record Books J.C. Jordan-Morris 1968-1969, 3 Item (Box-folder 156:1)
      - Teacher Record Books J.H. Prince-J. Puckhalier 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 156:2)
      - Teacher Record Books H.R. Redden-L. Shannon 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 156:3)
      - Teacher Record Books B. Shinault-C.B. Snowden 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 156:4)
      - Teacher Record Books Stacy-J.E. Thompson 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 156:5)
      - Teacher Record Books J.E. Thompson-Wainwright 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 157:1)
      - Teacher Record Books Wainwright-B.S. Wescott 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 157:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Whitecraft-E.V. Yancey 1968-1969, 3 Items (Box-folder 157:3)
      - Teacher Record Books Artinian L.M. Brown 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 157:4)
      - Teacher Record Books F.C. Bryant-Burnet 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 157:5)
      - Teacher Record Books J. Clark-Coogan 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 158:1)
      - Teacher Record Books A.T. Coogan-E.F. Dickerman 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 158:2)
      - Teacher Record Books M. Duren-Geitgey 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 158:3)
      - Teacher Record Books L.L. GIanokos-J.B. Green 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 158:4)
      - Teacher Record Books A.L. Hahn-W.J. Heepe 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 158:5)
      - Teacher Record Books Horn-C. Jones 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 159:1)
      - Teacher Record Books J.C. Jordan-L.B. Leitch 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 159:2)
      - Teacher Record Books P. Morris-N. Pritchett 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 159:3)
      - Teacher Record Books Reese-M.N. Runkle 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 159:4)
      - Teacher Record Books B. Shinault-Smith 1969-1970, 4 Items (Box-folder 159:5)
      - Teacher Record Books C.B. Snowden-Stancill 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 160:1)
      - Teacher Record Books N. Smith-B.S. Wescott 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 160:2)
      - Teacher Record Books H.E. Wainwright-Wood 1969-1970, 3 Items (Box-folder 160:3)
      - Teacher Record Books J.W. Yates 1969-1970, 2 Items (Box-folder 160:4)
      - Teacher Record Books Armentrout-F.C. Bryant 1970-1971 Sep-Jun, 7 Items (Box-folder 161:1)
      - Teacher Record Books C. Burgess-Gingles 1970-1971 Sep-Jun, 6 Items (Box-folder 161:2)
      - Teacher Record Books D.G. Goings-M.F. Howard 1970-1971 Sep-Jun, 6 Items (Box-folder 161:3)
      - Teacher Record Books A.H. Johnson-P.L. Paquette 1970-1971 Sep-Jun, 5 Items (Box-folder 161:4)
      - Teacher Record Books L. Rogers-M. Wright 1970-1971 Sep-Jun, 6 Items (Box-folder 161:5)
      - Teacher Record Books Kearney 1970-1971, 1 Item (Box-folder 161:6)
      - Teacher Record Books P. Morris-M. Wright 1970-1971, 2 Items (Box-folder 161:7)
      - Teacher Record Books E. Barnes-B. Bryant 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 162:1)
      - Teacher Record Books F. Bryant-E.C. Burnet 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 162:2)
      - Teacher Record Books Burnell-Cecil 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 162:3)
      - Teacher Record Books E.R. Conley-E.F. Dickerson 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 162:4)
      - Teacher Record Books M.H. Duren-Ewoldt 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 162:5)
      - Teacher Record Books L.L. Gianokos-Goings 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 163:1)
      - Teacher Record Books J.W. Good-E.M. Hartless 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 163:2)
      - Teacher Record Books B.S. Hathaway-Horn 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 163:3)
      - Teacher Record Books M.A. Howard-L.B. Leitch 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 163:4)
      - Teacher Record Books R.A Meadows-P.L. Paquette 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 163:5)
      - Teacher Record Books Reesi-M.N. Runkle 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 164:1)
      - Teacher Record Books Shreue-Stancill 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 164:2)
      - Teacher Record Books B. Wescott-[Wilson] 1970-1971, 3 Items (Box-folder 164:3)
      - Teacher Record Books Wood-No Name 1970-1971, 2 Items (Box-folder 164:4)
      - Teacher Record Books Cook-A.M. Page N. d., 2 Items (Box-folder 164:5)
      - Teacher Record Books W.A. Rhodes-H.W. Shapiro N. d., 3 Items (Box-folder 165:1)
      - Teacher Record Books N.R. Smith-No Name N. d., 4 Items (Box-folder 165:2)
    - Teacher Record Grade Cards
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Baker N. d., 29 Items (Box-folder 166:1)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Barnes N. d., 34 Items (Box-folder 166:2)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Bell N. d., 30 Items (Box-folder 166:3)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Berne N. d., 30 Items (Box-folder 166:4)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Chase N. d., 32 Items (Box-folder 166:5)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Evans N. d., 32 Items (Box-folder 166:6)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Fentriss N. d., 32 Items (Box-folder 166:7)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Foster N. d., 32 Items (Box-folder 166:8)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Frescoln N. d., 28 Items (Box-folder 166:9)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Gaines N. d., 30 Items (Box-folder 166:10)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Henderson N. d., 28 Items (Box-folder 166:11)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Johnson N. d., 33 Items (Box-folder 166:12)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Kearney N. d., 31 Items (Box-folder 166:13)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Kennedy N. d., 3 Items (Box-folder 166:14)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards McKeith N. d., 31 Items (Box-folder 166:15)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Manning N. d., 28 Items (Box-folder 166:16)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Meredith N. d., 31 Items (Box-folder 166:17)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Self N. d., 30 Items (Box-folder 166:18)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Smith N. d., 31 Items (Box-folder 166:19)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Stacy N. d., 30 Items (Box-folder 166:20)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Swartz N. d., 27 Items (Box-folder 166:21)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Vallianos N. d., 29 Items (Box-folder 166:22)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Waters N. d., 31 Items (Box-folder 166:23)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Wilson N. d., 31 Items (Box-folder 166:24)
      - Teacher Record Grade Cards Wilson N. d., 29 Items (Box-folder 166:25)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Armentrout n. d., 28 Items (Box-folder 167:1)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Armstrong n. d., 26 Items (Box-folder 167:2)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Barnes n. d., 28 Items (Box-folder 167:3)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Brown n. d., 29 Items (Box-folder 167:4)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets B. Bryant n. d., 30 Items (Box-folder 167:5)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets F. Bryant n. d., 30 Items (Box-folder 167:6)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Bunnell n. d., 32 Items (Box-folder 167:7)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Burgess n. d., 28 Items (Box-folder 167:8)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Burnet n. d., 33 Items (Box-folder 167:9)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Carmichael n. d., 28 Items (Box-folder 167:10)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Cecil n. d., 33 Items (Box-folder 167:11)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Duren n. d., 31 Items (Box-folder 167:12)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Gingles n. d., 2 Items (Box-folder 167:13)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Goings n. d., 27 Items (Box-folder 167:14)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Good n. d., 31 Items (Box-folder 167:15)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Hartless n. d., 29 Items (Box-folder 167:16)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Hathaway n. d., 34 Items (Box-folder 167:17)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Horn n. d., 33 Items (Box-folder 168:1)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Howard n. d., 33 Items (Box-folder 168:2)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Johnson n. d., 28 Items (Box-folder 168:3)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Kearney n. d., 41 Items (Box-folder 168:4)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Leitch n. d., 33 Items (Box-folder 168:5)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Murchison n. d., 33 Items (Box-folder 168:6)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Paquette n. d., 32 Items (Box-folder 168:7)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Rogers n. d., 27 Items (Box-folder 168:8)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Shreve n. d., 30 Items (Box-folder 168:9)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Smith n. d., 28 Items (Box-folder 168:10)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Wescott n. d., 32 Items (Box-folder 168:11)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Woody n. d., 25 Items (Box-folder 168:12)
      - Teacher Record Grade Sheets Wright n. d., 35 Items (Box-folder 168:13)
- Folder: Photocopies of the images from printing blocks of schools, licenses and certificates. In addition there are the original printing blocks., # Items
- Trophies from school sporting events such as football…, # Items
  Reel to Reel Tapes
- 40 items
  - April 18, 1968 Peabody Report Speeches and Activities 0298 (Reel 1)
  - November 21, 1968 Regular Meeting 0298-a (Reel 2)
  - December 19, 1968 Regular Meeting 0298-b (Reel 3)
  - January 16, 1969 Regular Meeting 0298-c (Reel 4)
  - January 27, 1969 Board Conference Budget 0298-d (Reel 5)
  - January 29, 1969 Special Meeting 0298-e (Reel 6)
  - February 3, 1969 City Council/School Board Conference and School Board Budget Study 0298-f (Reel 7)
  - February 10, 1969 Budget Meeting 0298-g (Reel 8)
  - February 18, 1969 Study Session Budget 0298-h (Reel 9)
  - February 20, 1969 Regular Meeting 0298-i (Reel 10)
  - March 20, 1969 Regular Meeting 0298-j (Reel 11)
  - April 17, 1969 Regular Meeting 0298-k (Reel 12)
  - May 5, 1969 Board/City Council 0298-l (Reel 13)
  - May 21, 1969 Board Conference 0298-m (Reel 14)
  - May 23, 1969 Special Meeting 0298-n (Reel 15)
  - June 9, 1969 Board Council 0298-o (Reel 16)
  - July 17, 1969 Part 1 0298-p (Reel 17)
  - July 17, 1969 Part II 0298-q (Reel 18)
  - July 17, 1969 Part III 0298-r (Reel 19)
  - August 21, 1969 Regular Meeting 0298-s (Reel 20)
  - September 18, 1969 Regular Meeting 0298-t (Reel 21)
  - October 14, 1969 NAACP Board Conference 0298-u (Reel 22)
  - October 14, 1969 Part I NAACP Board Conference 0298-v (Reel 23)
  - October 16, 1969 Regular Meeting 0298-w (Reel 24)
  - October 23, 1969 School Board C. E. A. 0298-x (Reel 25)
  - November 3, 1969 School Board Principals 0298-y (Reel 26)
  - November 20, 1969 Regular Meeting 0298-z (Reel 27)
  - December 15, 1969 Regular Meeting 0298-aa (Reel 28)
  - January 15, 1970 Regular Meeting 0298-ab (Reel 29)
  - February 12, 1970 Special Meeting Site Selection 0298-ac (Reel 30)
  - February 19, 1970 Regular Meeting 0298-ad (Reel 31)
  - March 19, 1970 Regular Meeting 0298-ae (Reel 32)
  - March 31, 1970 Special Meeting 0298-af (Reel 33)
  - April 16, 1970 Regular Meeting 0298-ag (Reel 34)
  - May 4, 1970 Regular Meeting 0298-ah (Reel 35)
  - May 21, 1970 Regular Meeting 0298-ai (Reel 36)
  - June 18, 1970 Regular Meeting 0298-aj (Reel 37)
  - June 30 [1970] Special Meeting 0298-ak (Reel 38)
  - July 16, 1970 Part I Regular Meeting 0298-al (Reel 39)
  - July 16, 1970 Part II Regular Meeting 0298-am (Reel 40)
- 46 items
  - September 17, 1970 Regular Meeting 0298-an (Reel 1)
  - October 15, 1970 Regular Meeting 0298-ao (Reel 2)
  - November 19, 1970 Regular Meeting 0298-ap (Reel 3)
  - February 17, 1972 Regular Meeting 0298-aq (Reel 4)
  - November 18, 1976 Regular Meeting 0298-ar (Reel 5)
  - November 30, 1976 Special Meeting Part I 0298-as (Reel 6)
  - November 30, 1976 Special Meeting Part II 0298-at (Reel 7)
  - November 30, 1976 Special Meeting Part III 0298-au (Reel 8)
  - November 30, 1976 Special Meeting Part IV 0298-av (Reel 9)
  - March 17 and April 7, 1977 Regular Meeting and Continuation of of Study Session 0298-aw (Reel 10)
  - April 7, 1977 Study Session 0298-ax (Reel 11)
  - April 21, 1977 Regular Meeting Venable School 0298-ay (Reel 12)
  - August 18, 1977 Regular Meeting 0298-az (Reel 13)
  - September 15, 1977 Regular Meeting 0298-ba (Reel 14)
  - October 20, 1977 Regular Meeting 0298-bb (Reel 15)
  - November 17, 1977 Regular Meeting 0298-bc (Reel 16)
  - December 15, 1977 Regular Meeting 0298-bd (Reel 17)
  - February 16, 1978 Regular Meeting 0298-be (Reel 18)
  - April 20, 1978 Regular Meeting 0298-bf (Reel 19)
  - April 20, 1978 Regular Meeting 0298-bg (Reel 20)
  - May 18, 1978 Regular Meeting 0298-bh (Reel 21)
  - June 15, 1978 Regular Meeting 0298-bi (Reel 22)
  - August 17, 1978 Regular Meeting 0298-bj (Reel 23)
  - September 15, 1978 Regular Meeting 0298-bk (Reel 24)
  - October 19, 1978 Regular Meeting 0298-bl (Reel 25)
  - November 6, 1978 Budget Study Session with Teachers 0298-bm (Reel 26)
  - November 16, 1978 Executive Session/John Wright and Regular School Board 0298-bn (Reel 27)
  - November 30, 1978 School Board Study Session (Budget) 0298-bo (Reel 28)
  - December 21, 1978 Regular Meeting 0298-bp (Reel 29)
  - January 18, 1979 Regular Meeting 0298-bq (Reel 30)
  - February 22, 1979 Regular Meeting 0298-br (Reel 31)
  - March 8, 1979 School Board Alternative Education Meeting 0298-bs (Reel 32)
  - March 15, 1979 Regular Meeting 0298-bt (Reel 33)
  - April 19, 1979 [Meeting] 0298-bu (Reel 34)
  - May 17, 1979 Regular Meeting 0298-bv (Reel 35)
  - May 29, 1979 Special Meeting [NAACP] Part I 0298-bw (Reel 36)
  - May 29, 1979 Special Meeting Student Achievement Study Hearing Part II 0298-bx (Reel 37)
  - June 6, 1979 School Board Committee 0298-by (Reel 38)
  - June 7, 1979 Study Session 0298-bz (Reel 39)
  - June 21, 1979 Regular Meeting 0298-ca (Reel 40)
  - June 30, 1979 School Board Retreat 0298-cb (Reel 41)
  - July 6, 1979 [Meeting] 0298-cc (Reel 42)
  - July 19, 1979 Regular Meeting 0298-cd (Reel 43)
  - August 2, 1979 Study Session 0298-ce (Reel 44)
  - August 16, 1979 School Board/City Council Luncheon Meeting Part I 0298-cf (Reel 45)
  - August 16, 1979 Regular Meeting Part II 0298-cg (Reel 46)
- Reel to Reels, 7 items
  - n. d. Betty Pitman and Lucille Bowen Study Group at Lane 0299 (Reel 1)
  - n. d. Mary Lockhart 0299-a (Reel 2)
  - n. d. Dr. Rushton, [Elizabeth] Bowen 0299-b (Reel 3)
  - n. d. inaudible tape #1 0299-c (Reel 4)
  - n. d. inaudible tape #2 0299-d (Reel 5)
  - n. d. inaudible tape #3 0299-e (Reel 6)
  - n. d. inaudible tape #4 [board meeting or panel discussion] 0299-f (Reel 7)